There are many different variations of snake arms.
They go from absolutely large, huge slow snake arms to a little bit smaller.
We are going to go over a low snake arm.
Sometimes the upper movements will hurt your shoulder so you want to make sure that you are not bothering your shoulder in this movement.
You can also refer to our arm drills to help to train your body for this movement as well.
So we are going to start with our elbow.
The elbow is going to lift up and the wrist is going to lift up.
Then the elbow is going to drop.
Then the wrist is going to drop.
The elbow is going to go up, wrist up, elbow drop, wrist drop.
Now, the beautiful part of this move is in the transition from here to here.
So you want to make sure your elbow is coming up and then you?re rolling down here.
Now watch the hand, make sure the hand doesn't fly around.
Our palm is facing in and then the palm is facing out, as if your brush your fingertips along the wall.
Up and down, and you want to drill with both arms.
Up and down, again elbow, wrist, elbow, wrist.
Elbow, wrist, when you add both arms together that's the tricky part.
So you want to drill each arm separately before adding them together.
One, two, switch, three.
Practice in front of a mirror so you can really watch yourself and make sure your doing them correctly.